# **Kaung San Hein**

I am a passionate web and mobile developer with three years of experience. A quick learner by nature. I love challenges and solving problems. Currently, I am working at The Union Myanmar as a web and mobile developer.

Mandalay, Myanmar 09782696857 kaungsanhein2019@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **The Union Myanmar**(Mandalay, Myanmar) - Web Developer

Since 10/06/2022 - now

I have been developing web and mobile applications for DOT management for TB patients at The Union Myanmar and also developing TB patients management dashboard.

## Real Code Solutions(Mandalay, Myanmar) - Web Developer

Since 01/06/2021 - 01/06/2022

I developed the website of Kakehashi Japanese Language Center by using Nextjs at Real Code Solution. This project has taken more than one month to finish. I got many experiences with Nextjs. Especially, I got to know about Nextjs because this project is my first project for me using Nextjs.

I assisted my senior colleague in creating the PoS mobile application by using Flutter at Real Code Solution. This project has taken more than four months to finish. I got many experiences with Flutter. Especially, I learned about how to connect a Flutter Application with a printer device and how to print a receipt.

I developed the official website of Real Code Solutions by using Nextjs and Strapi (the backend of the post features in it). This project has taken more than two months to finish. I got many experiences with Nextjs and Strapi. Especially, I knew about Strapi because this project was my first project for me using Strapi.

I only developed the web-based POS system using laravel, reactjs, and flutter. This project has taken about two months to finish. I faced many bugs and also got much pressure but got many experiences with that project, especially since I knew about Cpanel and how to manage developing time. And then, I continued responsible for that project (eg. creating an account, data import, and also software training) and have been developing customized software based on it.

I developed the project (Heaven Praise) using laravel, reactjs, and flutter with my senior. But I was responsible for the mobile app. I got to experience notification and messaging functions. Messaging function included sending text, docs, xlsx, pdf, and voice messages.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Dart, Reactjs, Nextjs, Nodejs, Laravel, Flutter, MySQL, Postgresql, MongoDB, Sqlite, Figma, Cpanel, VPS, Docker

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

**Portfolio Website** 

**GitHub** 

# IT One MM(Mandalay, Myanmar) - Junior Web Developer

01/05/2020 - 30/09/2020

I developed the backend of this application with my teacher from IT ONE MM by using Laravel, Reactjs, and Postgresql. This project has taken three months to finish. I got many experiences with Laravel(API), Reactjs, and Postgresql. Especially, We were developing this project with the first data structure from a client but after a few days, the data structure changed. So, We used a recursive function to create the new data structure. That is why I knew about a recursive function.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Yadanabon University(Mandalay, Myanmar)**— B.Sc (Computer Science)

2015 - 2019

I graduated B.Sc(Computer Science) from Yadanabon University in 2019. I have learned about C++, Java, C#, HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, and MySQL. I also learned about the software development life cycle. I developed the final project (Library Management System) by using HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, and MySQL. I also developed academic-level projects when I was a student. I pushed those projects on the GitHub account.

### **PROJECTS**

I have developed the following software and websites by using laravel, reactjs, and flutter.

I expressed the taking a responsible part in the below projects with brackets. I have also developed many other applications that are difficult to show because they were admin dashboards.

Phone Book App(laravel, reactjs)

**Kakehashi Website**(nextjs)

Real Code Solutions Website (nextjs)

<u>Point of Sale App and web-based POS system</u>(laravel, reactjs, flutter)

<u>Top power group App</u>(laravel, flutter)

<u>မာသင် App</u>(flutter, laravel, reactjs)

My Mobile App(laravel)

<u>Heaven Praise</u>(flutter, laravel, reactjs)